<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[MustafaGuvenc]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[MustafaGuvenc]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/mustafaguvenc/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 08:39:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/mustafaguvenc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who is Mustafa Güvenç]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Born at 1982 in Nişantaşı as first child of a mom from Hopa and a dad from İstanbul. Studied GeoPhysical Engineering at İstanbul Technical University. Just after the year that graduated from lycée, he founded a “computer shop” with a friend from lycée. He specialized at Network architecture and network security; software architecture and Linux applications of these. Build own firewall with a open source community, and sold at “computer shop”. Unfortunately, He got an offer from AirTies Wireless Networks for new conducting RnD. He worked as test engineer, test engineering manager. He conducted a field application engineering department and managed; also conducted a systems engineering department and managed. Finally, he become principle engineer at RnD. After these RnD adventure, he has been working as technical product manager at AirTies Wireless Networks until leaving the company. Since he likes to share his experiences and knowledge, actual reason is just being “smartass”, he is a mentor at İTÜ Cekirdek and guest lecturer at Bahçeşehir University. He is currently running his own advisory and consultancy business. Also, he is advising and mentoring at Proline Ventures. He is consultant to CEO of Proline Integrated Intelligence. At his spare time, he likes to sail, study about history, motorcycling, reading poems, playing turn based or realtime strategy games. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mustafaguvenc/who-is-mustafa-guvenc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">68e9324d-7582-48b3-8a5f-ecf194119434</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 08:39:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mustafa Güvenç Kimdir?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0bae79aa-9176-43d5-aac7-71e01851e625.png" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mustafaguvenc/mustafa-guvenc-kimdir/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">99648ba9-8988-4ba3-8e50-8f68fd05c6af</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 08:34:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>